[{
	"title": "Question 1.1",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 5,
	"answer": "3333"
}, {
	"title": "Question 1.2",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 10,
	"answer": "thousand"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.1",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 15,
	"answer": "8357"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.2",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 20,
	"answer": "alpine"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.3",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 10,
	"answer": "bill2"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.4",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 20,
	"answer": "2 columns"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.5",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 20,
	"answer": "4888"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.6",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 10,
	"answer": "999"
}, {
	"title": "Question 3.1",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 5,
	"answer": "8"
}, {
	"title": "Question 3.2",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 20,
	"answer": "111"
}, {
	"title": "Question 3.3",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 5,
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"title": "Question 3.4",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 5,
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"title": "Question 3.5",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 20,
	"answer": "x"
}, {
	"title": "Question 2.5",
	"question": "See samsclass",
	"points": 30,
	"answer": "frog"
}]